Dima Pidko

React Front-End Dev.

ABOUT

I am 22 years old student at V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University and get skills on Udemy platform. My first attempts at writing code were back in school, then i realized that i liked solving various problems with different levels of complexity and this became the starting point in the world of IT. After entering the university in 2019, i began a deep study of programming, which i continue to study to this day.

EDUCATION

Bachelor, 105 - Applied physics and nanomaterials

V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University

2019 - 2023, Kharkiv

Web-Developer, JavaScript + React/Redux uDemy

2023 - present

EXPERIENCE

Technical Task for IT school (pet project)

React dev, 2024 - Now

Here I created an application to join an IT school and improve my knowledge in Web development. The project turned out to be not so difficult, but some points made me think. When creating the project, I consolidated my knowledge of React / react-router-dom / styles module / REST API / OOP principles. Strengthened knowledge in component life cycle / component state / passing functions through

props. GitHubLink

World Sea Temperature (pet project)

React dev, 2024 - Now

The task was to draw a temperature map of the world's oceans from an input bit file. Here I tried to use TypeScript to catch bugs at the coding stage. After completing this task, I learned to use the built-in JavaScript reader of bit information from a file, and also used the "DRY" principle. I now understand how <canvas> works. **GitHubLink**

pidkodima@gmail.com +380668370182 Kharkiv

Industry Knowledge

React
JavaScript
HTML5 / CSS3
GIT / GitHub
Understanding SOLID / DRY
/ OOP

Languages

Ukrainian (native)
English (Intermediate)

Social

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dima-pidko-0ab8512ab/

https://github.com/ DimaPidko

https://t.me/ditsmon